George Brata

Senior Frontend Web Developer Cluj-Napoca, Romania





Summary

Versatile frontend web developer with broad experience using all kinds of UI frameworks, but my favorite stack (at the moment) is **Vue.js** and **Nuxt.js**. Very passionate about people, the Internet and blockchain technology - and everything that connects the three.

Experience

Senior Vue.js Developer, SHE Information Technology

Jan 2021 - May 2022

My responsibilities were maintaining a web platform based on FirstSpirit CMS, creating new Vue.js components and providing support for multilingual content teams across the world.

Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

Vue.js Developer, Salt&Pepper

Worked with a remote Maltese team to build and deliver an online casino. We created new functionalities using a proprietary frontend framework built on top of Vue.js with Typescript.

Jun 2018 - Dec 2019

Frontend Web Developer, QCatalyst

Building, testing, deploying and maintaining responsive consumer-facing web applications for National Geographic using modern technologies like React, Redux, TailwindCSS, Webpack, Storybook and Jest.

Apr 2017 - May 2018

UI Developer, 3Pillar Global

Developed financial education learning modules for a US-based client in a React.js app. As a team, we worked with tools like Github, CircleCl, JIRA, Browserstack and Confluence to deliver high-quality readable code and documentation.

Jun 2016 - Mar 2017

Junior Web Developer, Yonder

Migrated a legacy app from Microsoft Silverlight to AngularJS and built the frontend of a completely new web app from scratch using Angular.js 2 and Bulma CSS.

Feb 2016 - May 2016

Intern Web Development, Yonder

Learned the basics of web development - HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery. In the last month, we built a small web multiplayer game using Flask (a Python framework), Bootstrap, and SocketIO.

Feb 2016 - present

Trainer, Digital Kids Cluj

During weekends, I teach children the computer skills they need to thrive in the 21st century, including the basics of programming, photo/video editing, robotics, and other digital abilities.

Education

2014 - 2017 2010 - 2014 Computer Science B.Sc., Babes-Bolyai University, Cluj-Napoca Mathematics - Informatics, Emanuil Gojdu High School, Oradea

Why hire me?

Results-driven and people-oriented, I am feeling comfortable in any kind of dev environment - corporate or start-up. I get excited about crafting modern web applications and continuously delivering top-notch functionalities with great UX. Beside my regular frontend developer job, over the last 6 years I have built several <u>personal side-projects</u> and I went to a <u>dozen hackathons</u> to train exactly those muscles.